gett.com 2017-02-17

# Privacy Policy | Gett

### Privacy Policy

#### Gett Privacy Policy

**  Last updated: July 30, 2015**

The Website www.gett.com (the “ **Site** ”) and Our mobile software application (the “ **App** ”) are operated by GT Forge, Inc. dba Get Taxi, located at 237 West 35th Street, New York, New York 10001 (“ **We, Our or Us** ”). This Privacy Policy, along with Our Terms of Use (available at http://tu.gett.com), set forth the information practices of the Site and App, including Our collection, use and disclosure of information.

We are committed to safeguarding any personal information collected on the Site and the App. We ensure that Our Privacy Policy and information practices conform to the applicable data privacy laws and all other applicable legislation.

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time at Our sole discretion. We will inform users of the Site and App of any such amendments by posting a new Privacy Policy on the Site home page including a clear indication of the new effective date. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, users include anyone who accesses or registers for the Site or App (together, “ **User** ” or “ **Users** ”). As required by law, we will not use personal information in ways that are materially different from the ones set forth in this Privacy Policy without providing notification of such practices and obtaining consent. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post a notice of these changes on the Site and in this Privacy Policy and, to the extent required by applicable law, we will obtain Users’ consent. Users are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information a User provides to us while visiting or using Our Site or App. Information a User may provide in visiting or using Our Site or App falls into two broad categories: Personally Identifiable Information (“ **PII** ”) and Aggregate Information (“ **AI** ”). PII is information that is personal to a User and which can be used to identify or contact a User, including first and last name, home or other physical address including street name and city or town, email address, telephone number, Social Security number, or any other identifying information that would permit physical or online contact with a User. Aggregate Information is information that does not identify a User, and may include, for example, statistical information concerning the sections of Our Site and App that Users most frequent and Users’ activities on the Site and App. Our Privacy Policy governs both categories of information, as detailed below.

**_1\. Information We Collect_**

**1.1        _Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”)_**

During the registration process, we directly collect certain information from you, including your name, a functioning email address where you can be reached, a password of your selection, and a method of payment. Some of this information is PII. We may not, and do not, require a User to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary to access and use Our Site and App. Users are not required by law to provide such information, but must provide it if they wish to become a registered user of the Site and App and receive additional communications as detailed in Sections 1.2 and 2 of this Privacy Policy.

We may engage third parties to collect PII from Users. The types of information that may be collected and stored at that time include the payer’s full name, e-mail address, credit card billing information including mailing address, and such other information as may be requested from time to time. That information is safeguarded with appropriate security and it will not be used for other purposes. The third parties we engage to collect payment information from Our users have agreed to maintain the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal and financial information they obtain from Site and App users, and to only use this information on Our behalf. **We encourage all Users to read the privacy policies and other terms of such third parties’ websites before using their services.**

If a User does not provide certain PII to us, then we may not permit that User’s Site or App registration and that User may be denied access to certain content and other functions on the Site or App, or other information, products or services.

**1.2        ****_Aggregate Information (“AI”)_**

AI includes information concerning Users’ activities on the Site and App (including, but not limited to, statistical information about which pages are visited, the date and time of the visits, other User activities and how long Users view the Site pages) and information Users’ browser sends whenever Users visit a website (such as computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web pages that were visited before visiting the Site and App).

When a User uses a widget or any other tool offered by us, whether on the Site or App or on a third party website, including a website owned or operated by a User, we may record data related to that activity, the deployment of the widget or tool, and any other account related data.

We or a third party acting on Our behalf may collect this AI through the use of technology such as unique identifiers, or “cookies,” as set forth in Section 1.3.

**1.3** **        _Cookies_**

We use “cookies” to save user name, password and language selection for future log-ins to the Site and App, to better understand how Users interact with the Site and App, and to monitor web traffic routing on, and aggregate usage of, the Site and App.

Cookies are small text files that a website can use to recognize repeat users, to facilitate the user’s ongoing access to and use of the website, and to compile aggregate data to improve the website. Cookies work as follows: we will send a cookie to a User’s browser that uniquely associates that User’s computer with information stored at the Site and App. That User’s browser places the cookie in its cookies file. When that User next accesses the Site or App, the Site or App recognizes the cookie, makes available the stored information (such as user names, password and language selection), and may add new information based on the present visit. For more information on how we use cookies, please see our Cookie Policy at <https://gett.com/cookie-policy.html>

**1.4        _Communications_**

We collect, store and may review records of communications that Users send to the Site or via the App. When a User sends email or other communications to us, regardless of whether or not the communication contains PII, we may retain those communications in order to process that User’s inquiries, respond to requests, and improve Our services.

Users are free at any time to opt-out of receiving email and other information we may send to them by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in such communications, or by contacting us at [CC-NYC@GETT.COM](mailto:CC-NYC@GETT.COM), or by sending written notification by registered mail to Our address set forth in Section 6. However, it is important to us that we may send communications to the email address indicated as the User’s email address during the registration process. If a User elects to opt-out of receiving emails regarding compliance with the Site’s and App’s Terms and Conditions and other rules and policies to such email address, we may immediately terminate that User’s account and membership with, and access to, and use of the Site and App.

**1.5.       _Other Websites, Third Party Surveys and Questionnaires_**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the Site and App. The Site and App may contain links and references to websites of others. We may, from time to time, at Our sole discretion, add or remove links to other websites. These links are provided solely as a convenience to you, and access to any such websites is at your own risk. We may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. In addition, third party companies and individuals which we use to perform services related to administration of the Site and App (including without limitation bill and credit card payment processing), and other websites, and sweepstakes, rewards, contests of skill, or promotions, may place their own cookies or other files on Users’ computers or collect data or solicit PII directly from Our Users. Likewise, Users may receive requests through the Site and App to participate in third party surveys and questionnaires which may include disclosure of Users’ PII.

We do not review, approve, monitor, endorse, guarantee, warrant, make any representations with respect to, nor are We responsible for, such links or websites. In no event will We be responsible for the information contained in such links or websites, their practices or for your use of or inability to use such links or websites or their services, or transmissions received from such sites. By using the Site, you expressly relieve Us from any and all liability arising from your use of any third-party website.

Other websites may follow different rules regarding the collection, use or disclosure of PII that you submit. PII that Our Users provide to those other websites may be sent to us in order to enable Our Users’ use of the Site and App. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Other websites may have different privacy practices. **We encourage Users to read the privacy policies and other terms and familiarize themselves with the privacy practices of the other websites before using their services.**

**1.5        _Children Under the Age of Thirteen_**

The Site and App are not directed at children under the age of 13 and We do not knowingly collect any PII from children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that the Site or App have collected the PII of a child under the age of 13, please contact Us at [CC-NYC@GETT.COM](mailto:CC-NYC@GETT.COM) or by registered mail to Our address at 237 West 35th Street, New York, New York 10001.

**2. _How We Use, Store and Disclose the Information We Collect_**

**2.1        _Collection, Storage and Use_.**

We may collect, store and use information Users provide to us on Our Site and App to:

  * enable Users to log-in into the Site and App;
  * administer use of the Site and App and Users’ Site and App accounts, including, but not limited to, communications at the email address provided during registration to provide notification regarding the Site or App, such as any future amendments to its privacy practices or this Privacy Policy;
  * ensure all Users follow Our Terms and Conditions and other rules and policies;
  * ban a User temporarily or permanently for failure to follow Our Terms and Conditions, rules and policies, or for other misconduct or inappropriate behavior;
  * respond to questions and comments from Users;
  * provide Users with newsletters, updates, and other materials related to the purposes of the Site and App, or with information or offers from us or third parties that we believe Users may find useful or interesting;
  * monitor and analyze the Site and App (including, but not limited to, measuring Users’ interest in and use of various areas of the Site and App);
  * improve the functionality, design and quality of the Site and App;
  * perform the technical administration of the Site and App;
  * investigate cases of suspected abuse or fraud;
  * prepare statistical and other summary analyses of Our Users’ behavior;
  * as provided below.

We do not save or retain User credit card or debit card information in the App or on or in connection with the Site.

**2.2        _Service Providers and Other Third Parties_**

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate the operation of the Site and App, and to perform services related to administration of the Site and App (including, but not limited to, bill and credit card payment processing, maintenance, hosting and database management services, web analytics and administration). These third parties have access to Users’ PII only to perform these tasks on Our behalf.

We may share AI, and reports based on AI, with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, other commercial purposes, or to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. No such AI that we provide to third parties will contain PII.

**2.3        _Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement_**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about Users, including PII, to government or law enforcement officials or private parties where we are required to do so by law, including, but not limited to, in response to a court order or subpoena. We may also disclose PII in response to a request by a law enforcement agency or other public agency (including, but not limited to, schools or children services) or if we believe such disclosure may prevent or mitigate the threat of crime or harm to Users or others, facilitate an investigation related to a User’s safety or public safety, protect the security or integrity of Our Site and App, or enable us to take precautions against liability.

This Privacy Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, notwithstanding choice or conflict of laws issues. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision or portion of this Privacy Policy to be unenforceable, the remainder of the Privacy Policy will continue in full force and effect.

  * **_Business Transfers_**

In connection with a sale of all or part of Our business, or sale or transfer of assets, or an acquisition, merger, reorganization, or in the event of bankruptcy, we may transfer PII to a third party as part o the transaction, to the extent permitted by applicable law.

  3. **_Security and How We Safeguard Information We Collect_**

The security of Users’ information is important to us. We have put in place appropriate security systems designed to prevent unauthorized access to, disclosure and use of information Users provide to us. These systems are structured to deter and prevent hackers and others from accessing this information. Due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, however, we cannot provide, and expressly disclaim, any assurance that the information provide to us will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties who, despite Our efforts, obtain unauthorized access.

  4. **_How To Obtain Access to Information You Provide, And To Remove or Change It_**

Users may review, update, or correct your PII by logging onto the Site and clicking the User data icon or by changing it in the App.

Users may, to the extent permitted by law, request the deletion of their PII, unless we are required to retain such information by law. Please contact us as set forth in Section 6 if you would like to access the PII we have collected online from you, correct errors in such PII, request to have the PII deleted or no longer collected or maintained. The deletion of data shall effectively terminate your User account and membership with, and access to, and use of the Site and App. We reserve the right to verify the identity of any person making an opt-out or correct/update request, but shall have no liability whatsoever resulting from false or erroneous requests.

We may in Our discretion delete any information provided by a User or related to a User, pursuant to Our policies as then in effect, to the extent permitted by applicable law.

  5. **_International Processing or Transfer_**

To the extent permitted by applicable law, your information may be processed or transferred outside of your state, where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

  6. **_Inadvertent Disclosure of PII_**

You acknowledge and accept that, despite our efforts, there may be times or situations when your PII is inadvertently disclosed by Us or by a third party to whom we have disclosed Your PII. You hereby accept that risk and waive any and all claims, causes of action, damages and liability against Us in the event of inadvertent or negligent disclosure of PII.

  7. **_Contacting Us_**

If you have any concerns or questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [CC-NYC@GETT.COM](mailto:CC-NYC@GETT.COM) or by registered mail to Our address at 237 West 35th Street, New York, New York 10001.

Copyright 2015, GT Forge, Inc. d/b/a Gett. All rights reserved.
